webaffair.com 2011-08-05

# Dating : Free Online Dating at WebAffair.com

WebAffair.com ("Website")is committed to respecting and safeguarding your privacy online as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy statement sets forth the policies and practices with respect to information or data that is received or gathered regarding users of this Website.

**VISITOR INFORMATION**

If you visit this Website we will collect and store only the following non-personally identifying information from you; the name of the domain name from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access our Website; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Website. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our Website, to help us make our Website more useful to visitors, and to measure the amount of traffic generated through our affiliate network with whom this information may be shared.

The only other personally-identifying information we collect and store about you is the information you choose to provide to us, such as your username, e-mail address, address, zip code, etc. In addition, we may ask you to submit certain personal information when you order products form us for billing and shipping purposes. When you provide your personally identifiable information on this Website, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of such information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

If a user sends any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the Website, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the Website may collect any information regarding that communication and include that information in its database.

This Website is intended for adults. We do not knowingly collect and store personal information from children who are under the age of Thirteen years old.

**COOKIES**

This Website uses cookies to store and sometimes track information to make your online experience easier and more personalized. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Most major Web browsers are set up so that they will initially accept cookies, but you may modify your computers preferences to issue you an alert when a cookie is downloaded, or to disable the ability of third parties to download a cookie to you. If you choose to reject all cookies, there are areas of this and other websites that may not function properly.

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AND DISCLAIMER**

By the use of the Website or its products and services, the user expressly agrees that the Website may use any information that it gathers or collects about the user including personal information that has been provided by the user for technical, administration, research and development, customer administration, marketing, promotional and advertising use and for the transmission of email communications, the sending of products or the fulfilling of any terms and conditions; and furthermore that the Website may disclose or provide such personal information to its affiliates, agents and service providers that provide customer support, fulfillment, merchant processing or any other goods and services, for purposes of providing such goods and services. We may also share personally identifiable information with marketing partners or other carefully selected vendors so they can send you notices about their products and services.

The Website is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a user may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the Website. This Website does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or Privacy Policies of any of those third-party websites, and those third-party websites may have different privacy policies than this Website. Whenever applicable, each user should seek to read the Privacy Policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the Website.

All Members, visitors and Users of this Website should consider any information provided to or collected by the Website as non-confidential, and consequently the Website assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any user is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.

**DISCLOSURE**

WebAffair.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except in accordance with this Privacy Policy or when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating any of our Terms and Conditions.

**E-MAIL COMMUNICATIONS**

When you purchase goods or services from this website we may send you e-mailed transactional communications regarding you purchase such as order, billing and shipping information, customer service communications such as product updates, etc.).

WebAffair.com is committed to respecting and safeguarding your privacy online. We do not sell or rent your e-mail address to others. On occasion we may send you e-mail communications describing special offers, discounts and new products either from the operators of the Website, its agents, affiliates or other third-parties (collectively referred to as "Offers"). If you prefer not to receive such Offers, or subsequently choose to revoke or withdraw any consent to receive such Offers in the future you may Opt-Out sending an e-mail to cs@WebAffair.com.

**REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Website reserves the right, in its sole and absolute discretion, to revise, amend, modify or revoke this Privacy Policy at any time and in any manner. Changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective by posting revisions on this Web site. This privacy policy is not intended to, and does not, create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
